

420 N Roosevelt St, Bloomington, IN 47408 I C: 812-287-3749 I Email: songxini365@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Senior graphic designer with more than 15 years experience in product design, design of print and web media, as well as publishing. I am an enthusiastic and creative visual designer with exceptional creativity, resourcefulness and efficiency.

HIGHLIGHTS

- self-motivated professional
- creative and artistic
- highly efficient, disciplined worker
- teamwork
- quick learner
- multilingual (English, German, Chinese)
- IT-skills (PC/Mac)

Adobe Creative Suite, CSS, html, Office, After Effects, Premiere, Coreldraw, Painter, Macro- media Flash MX, DVD Studio Pro, Encore

- layouting and print design
- · corporate identity design
- logo design
- video production
- web page creation and enhancement
- photography
- book design
- oil paintings

ACCOMPLISHMENT

2	2007	published in the "PAGE" magazine
		published in "Interfacedesign" from Prof. Torsten Stapelkamp
		"Designing the screen and interface for a utilisation of content for Phaenomedial with a PDA or smartphone."
:	2006	Interactive DVD-Production "Story of a Jazzpiano"
:	2005	Illustrations pulished in "Kleine digitale_Malklasse" from Karl Mueller
	1999	Exhibitions oil painting, watercolour painting and posters in different galleries in China.
	1990	Awards in "Arts and Calligraphy" on a regional and national level in China

EXPERIENCE

10/2013 - today	Indiana University, Psychological and Brain Sciences: design for Graspble Math Project
11/2006 - 07/2013	Viva Decor GmbH, Badsalzuflen, Germany:
	graphic design, webdesign, marketing, photography, production of a promotional film
	trade with China: marketing, product development
10/2005 - 10/2006	Sarbandi communication, healthcare advertising agency, Bielefeld, Germany:
	graphic- and webdesign
07/2000 - 12/2002	Siemens communications Networks Ltd., in Beijing, China:
	advertisement, Logo, poster, brochure, packaging, Lab interior design
07/2000 - 08/2003	Bauhaus Product Design company, Beijing, China: graphic design

EDUCATION

08/2011 - 2013	Business economics (BWL) Bielefeld, Germany. SGD (correspondence course of study)
09/2007 - 07/2009	Master of Arts (M.A.) FH Bielefeld, Germany. communications design - multimedia
01/2004 - 07/2006	Diploma Degree. FH Bielefeld, Germany. main focus: interactive multimedia
09/1996 - 07/2000	Bachelor Degree. Tsinghua University, Academy of Arts and Design, Beijing, China
	main focus: graphics design

WEBPAGE

http://graspablemath.com/projects/xini/6eck/ More samples available upon request.